deltek.com 2019-10-23

# Privacy Policy | Deltek

**I. Purpose**

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes our practices with respect to (i) the personal information we gather on our website (ii) the way we use personal information internally; and (iii) our policy regarding sharing your personal information with others. 

We are committed to processing your information in accordance with international legal standards, including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other applicable data protection laws and data protection codes of conduct. We have implemented the practices set out in this Privacy Policy for our website and dependent pages (the "Site"). We have instructed our website administrator to include information regarding these privacy practices anywhere on the Site where Personal Information is collected. 

This policy addresses our privacy practices relating to visitors to the Site and registered users of the Site. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information that, by itself or in combination with other information, identifies or can reasonably be used to identify an individual, such as name, email address, IP address, telephone number, address, billing information or date of birth. Personal Information does not include information that is anonymized, or publicly-available information. The term “Processing” means any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Information, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, use, organization, storage, alteration or destruction, disclosure, or transfer. This Privacy Policy does not cover Deltek Collaboration. Deltek Collaboration’s Privacy Policy may be found at [https://collaborate.deltekfirst.com/privacy](https://collaborate.deltekfirst.com/privacy/). 

DECLARATION OF CONSENT 

By submitting Personal Information and other information to the Site, you consent to the Processing of such information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

You may withdraw this consent at any time by notifying us at [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com), or by writing to Deltek, Inc., ATTN: Privacy Policy Inquiry, Herndon, Virginia 20171. 

**II. Scope**

This Privacy Policy does not cover data from which individual persons cannot be identified. 

Our website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to us through the Site. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not access, use, or provide any information on the Site or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us by sending us an email at [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com), or by writing to Deltek, Inc., ATTN: Privacy Policy Inquiry, Herndon, Virginia 20171. 

**III. Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Generally, you may browse the Site without providing any Personal Information. However, we may ask that you provide information, including, without limitation, Personal Information, at various times and locations through the Site. For example, if you decide to register with the Site to request information, you will be asked to provide information such as your name and email address. When using forms on the Site to communicate with us, you may choose to provide other Personal Information, such as your name, company name, mailing address, phone number, and email address. We may collect and store any Personal Information you input into the Site. 

The Personal Information collected by and through the Site may be used by Deltek, its divisions, holding companies, subsidiaries and affiliates, or other entities that are involved in the operation of the Site. We may use the information collected and provided, individually or in an aggregate form, in order to: 

  * contact you about the Site;
  * notify you about important changes to the Site;
  * evaluate products or services we could offer to you;
  * monitor or improve use of the Site;
  * compare and otherwise use data entered by users for any purpose including consulting, research and marketing;
  * customize any advertising and content you see on the Site;
  * provide specific information to you from us and/or our affiliates; and
  * send you promotional material from us and/or our affiliates.

We do not sell Personal Information about you to unrelated companies for their independent use. 

**IV. Disclosures/Onward Transfers of Personal Information**

Deltek discloses your Personal Information to those who reasonably need to know such data for a legitimate business purpose and as required by law to Deltek subsidiaries, third parties, and business partners. By using Deltek websites, products, and solutions, or by providing your Personal Information to Deltek, you consent to the potential transfer, processing, and storage of such information outside of your country of residence where data protection standards may be different than your own. 

Deltek requires our business partners, service vendors, authorized agents, and contractors to whom such disclosures are made to abide by confidentiality obligations. Absent your consent, Deltek will disclose your Personal Information only to service providers and their contractors who perform tasks on Deltek's behalf, provided that such service providers and/or contractors either: (a) comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield principles regarding the collection, use, sharing, and retention of personal information from the European Union or use another mechanism permitted by EU data protection laws and the applicable laws of other countries that impose international data transfer restrictions; or (b) agree to provide adequate protections for your privacy interests that are no less protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy and to use the Personal Information only for the purposes for which the third party has been engaged by Deltek. 

Deltek’s business partners are independent third parties that are otherwise not affiliated with Deltek. Any relationship a customer elects to enter into with a partner for products and services is directly between the respective customer and partner. 

Any Personal Information that you provide to us will be used for our purposes only. Personal Information will not be shared with individuals or other companies other than those referred to in this Privacy Policy. 

In some instances, however, we may need to provide Personal Information to third parties that we use to deliver specific products or services to you (such as shipping or direct mailing organizations). In such cases, our agreements with these third parties do not permit them to use Personal Information for purposes other than fulfilling those services or allow such third parties to further disclose your Personal Information.

We collect the domain names and IP addresses of our visitors for statistical purposes, to measure use, to improve the content or responsiveness of the Site, or to customize the content or layout of the Site for the individual visitor. We do not disclose this information to third parties. We may also aggregate information relating to our visitors' traffic patterns from the data that we collect and retain concerning the IP addresses and domain names of our visitors, and we may divulge such aggregate information about our users with third parties such as our business partners, distributors, and service and support providers. 

Data entered on the Site may be transferred to, and processed, on servers located in the countries in which we operate. Your data may be used by Deltek and its divisions, holding companies, subsidiaries and affiliates, or other entities outside the EU and the EEA including in the U.S. Please note that in countries outside the country in which you live, and in particular outside the EU/EEA, a different standard of data protection might apply than the standard that you are used to in your own country. By completing and submitting the contact form on our website, you acknowledge and consent that data will be transferred across international borders, including to countries outside the EU/EEA. Irrespective of which country you live in, you authorize Deltek to transfer, store, and use your information in the United States, Ireland, and any other country where we operate. In some of these countries, the privacy and data protection law and rules regarding when government authorities may access data may vary from those of the country in which you reside. 

The Site may contain links to other third-party sites. When you click on one of these links you are visiting a website operated by someone other than us and the operator of that website may have a different privacy policy. We are not responsible for their individual privacy practices, so we encourage you to investigate the privacy policies of such third-party operators. 

**V. Sensitive Data**

"Sensitive Data" is data that pertains to a person’s racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, income records, health, sexual orientation, or alleged commission of any offense. Deltek does not solicit Sensitive Data and, except as required by law, will not disclose Sensitive Data to any third party. Further, Deltek will not use your Sensitive Data for any purpose other than (1) for the purpose for which you originally provided it, (2) for a purpose you later expressly consented to, or (3) where necessary to fulfill Deltek’s legal obligations. 

**VI. Confidentiality and Security of Data**

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information when you transmit it from your computer to the Site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.

While every effort and measure is taken to reduce the risk of data breaches, we have dedicated controls and procedures in place for such situations, along with the procedures that are required to make notifications to the relevant Supervisory Authority and data subjects (where applicable). 

**VII. Right to Access, Change or Delete Data**

If you want us to correct your Personal Information or other information, or if you would like us to provide you with a copy of the Personal Information that we hold about you, or if you would like the Personal Information that we hold about you to be erased, please contact us by sending us an email at [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com) or writing to us at Deltek, Inc., ATTN: Privacy Policy Inquiry, Herndon, Virginia 20171. We will endeavor to respond to any such requests within 30 days of receipt.

For California Users: California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Site visitors who are California residents and who have provided us with "personal information" (as that term is defined in Section 1798.83) to request certain information about the disclosure of that information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you may contact us by writing to: Deltek, Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry, 2291 Wood Oak Drive, Herndon, Virginia 20171. 

For Canadian Users: Canadian citizens, except under circumstances defined by law, are entitled to access their own personal data collected by Deltek by writing to: Deltek, Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry, 2291 Wood Oak Drive, Herndon, Virginia 20171. If you believe that the personal data about you that we have collected is incomplete or inaccurate, please contact us and we will correct the information upon verification of the omission or error and of the identity of the person requesting the change. 

Personal Information will be stored for as long as the information is required to fulfill our legitimate business needs or the purposes for which the Personal Information was collected, or for such period as is required by law. 

**VIII. Use of Cookies**

Deltek uses cookies (small text files placed on your device) and similar technologies to enhance our websites and online services and help collect data. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie originated, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. This permits Deltek to provide you with a better experience when you browse our websites and also allows us to improve our sites and services. Deltek uses cookies and similar technologies for several purposes, depending on the product, including: 

  * Where they are essential to operate our websites;
  * To enable personalization features on our websites (which give you the ability to recall recently viewed pages and see information which you have input on line);
  * To compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our websites and to help us improve the structure of our websites; and
  * To better send you personalized offers.

For more detailed information about cookies, how they are used on our websites, and how to turn off our cookies, please see our Cookie Policy. 

**IX. Enabling or Disabling Cookies**

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but provide controls that allow you to block or delete them. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies from our websites at any time by modifying the settings in your web browser. Certain features of Deltek products depend on cookies. Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use those features, and preferences that are dependent on cookies may be lost. For further information about disabling cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.

**X. E-Mail Addresses**

You should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against all forms of interception. If your communication includes sensitive information about your company and you would prefer not to transmit this information in this fashion, please contact us by post or telephone rather than e-mail. 

We collect email addresses that are: volunteered by the visitor; through e-mail messages addressed to us or our employees; through visitor responses via the "contact us" portion of the Site; or e-mail marketing destination web pages and public events. We use e-mail addresses for marketing purposes and to inform those interested in our products about events, products, services or other items of interest. We may also use e-mail addresses volunteered by our visitors to register the visitor for an extranet account, to process orders for brochures and other written materials, or otherwise to respond to a visitor's request. 

On the Site we will ask you to consent to being contacted by us for promotional and marketing purposes. However, you may opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing emails at any time by notifying us as a reply to any unwanted e-mail, by using the unsubscribe function in our newsletter, contacting us at [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com), or by writing to us at Deltek, Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry, 2291 Wood Oak Drive, Herndon, Virginia 20171. Requests to unsubscribe from Deltek e-mails may take 5 business days to process. 

**XI. Log Files**

We maintain a log file of all actions that are initiated or facilitated using the Site, to capture, record and store data concerning the transaction. Access to this data is restricted to those who administer our network and public website, except that we may use and disclose this information to third parties in response to legal process or law enforcement inquiries, abuse of our website, or violation of any applicable Terms of Use or contractual provision you may have with us. 

**XII. Data Integrity**

You are responsible for the accuracy of the data that you provide to Deltek. Deltek will use reasonable efforts to maintain the accuracy and integrity of such data and update it as appropriate. Deltek will not maintain data any longer than necessary for the purposes stated unless you otherwise agree and as legally required. 

**XIII. Reporting Claims of Copyright Infringement**

We take claims of copyright infringement seriously. We will respond to notices of alleged copyright infringement that comply with applicable law. If you believe any materials accessible on or from collaborate.deltekfirst.com and/or govwin.com (the "Websites") infringe your copyright, you may request removal of those materials (or access to them) from the Websites by submitting written notification to our copyright agent designated below. In accordance with the Online Copyright Infringement Liability Limitation Act of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (17 U.S.C. § 512) ("DMCA"), the written notice (the "DMCA Notice") must include substantially the following: 

  * Your physical or electronic signature;
  * Identification of the copyrighted work you believe to have been infringed or, if the claim involves multiple works on the Website, a representative list of such works;
  * Identification of the material you believe to be infringing in a sufficiently precise manner to allow us to locate that material;
  * Adequate information by which we can contact you (including your name, postal address, telephone number, and, if available, email address);
  * A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the copyrighted material is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
  * A statement that the information in the written notice is accurate; and
  * A statement, under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner.

Our designated copyright agent to receive DMCA Notices is: 

Office of the General Counsel  
Attn: Compliance Counsel  
Deltek  
2291 Wood Oak Drive  
Herndon, Virginia 20171  
[dmca@deltek.com](mailto:dmca@deltek.com) or [legalcompliance@deltek.com](mailto:legalcompliance@deltek.com)

If you fail to comply with all of the requirements of Section 512(c)(3) of the DMCA, your DMCA Notice may not be effective. 

Please be aware that if you knowingly materially misrepresent that material or activity on the Website is infringing your copyright, you may be held liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) under Section 512(f) of the DMCA. 

**XIV. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is current as of the effective date set forth below. Deltek reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time, consistent with applicable data protection and privacy laws and principles. Unless such changes afford greater protections to your privacy interests, or you otherwise consent, such changes will apply only to Personal Information received after the effective date of such change. You should refer to this Privacy Policy regularly, as it will be updated from time to time. By continuing to access or use Deltek services after such revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

**XV. Questions or Complaints**

Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please let us know by contacting us at [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com) or writing to us at the address below: 

Deltek, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry  
2291 Wood Oak Drive  
Herndon, Virginia 20171 

**XVI. Enforcement**

As part of Deltek's privacy compliance process, Deltek will review its compliance with this Privacy Policy. We welcome comments and questions regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions, complaints, or disputes regarding the manner in which Deltek handles or protects your data, please bring it to the attention of [privacy@deltek.com](mailto:privacy@deltek.com). 

Updated: 25 May 2018
